A Guide to the Photographs of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1993
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Photographs of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1993
The Library of Virginia
35539
6.65 cu. ft. (19 boxes)
Virginia. Governor (1990-1994: Wilder)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder on 31 October 1996.
Biographical Information
Lawrence Douglas Wilder was born in Richmond, Va., on January 17, 1931. He graduated from Virginia Union University in 1951 and afterwards was drafted into the Army, where he served in the Korean War from 1952-1953 and received a bronze star. He then attended the Howard University School of Law and graduated in 1959. Douglas Wilder was elected to the Virginia Senate in 1969 as the first African American member since Reconstruction and served in the Senate for five terms. In 1985, he was elected to the office of Lieutenant Governor as the first African American to be elected to statewide office in Virginia. L. Douglas Wilder won the election for Governor of Virginia in 1989 and served from January 13, 1990 to January 14, 1994. He was the first African American to be elected as Governor in United States.
Scope and Content
Photographs, 1989-1993, from the office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder. The photographs are arranged numerically by photograph number, which is in basic chronological order. Includes photographs of events at the Executive Mansion, Inauguration, signing of bills, visits with various heads of state, summits, award presentations, General Assembly, parades, luncheons, and travels.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged numerically by photograph number.
Contents List
- 89-7410, Governor Wilder, 12/23/1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 90-0083, Gov. Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 90-0085, Gov. Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 90-0086, Gov. Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 90-0087, Gov. Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 90-0088, Gov. Wilder lights State Christmas tree and holds Open House at the Mansion, 12/14/1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 90-0089, Gov. Wilder addresses the General Assembly Money Committee, 12/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 90-0090, Gov. Wilder addresses the General Assembly Money Committee, 12/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 90-0091, Gov. Wilder receives a Bible from the Gideons, 12/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 90-0092, Family practice of Blackstone receives a reward and it was presented by Governor Wilder, 12/18/1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 90-7528, Cabinet Swearing, 1/14/1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 90-7529, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 90-7530, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 90-7531, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 90-7532, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 90-7533, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 90-7534, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 90-7535, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 90-7536, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 90-7537, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 90-7538, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 90-7539, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 90-7540, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 90-7541, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 90-7542, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- 90-7543, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 90-7544, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- 90-7545, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 90-7546, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- 90-7547, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 90-7548, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- 90-7549, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- 90-7550, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 90-7551, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 90-7553, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 90-7554, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 90-7555, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 90-7556, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 90-7557, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 90-7558, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 90-7560, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, Before and After Prayer Service Inauguration Reception at St. Paul's, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 90-7561, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, Jefferson Hotel: pinning of flowers learning for motorcade, and passing mansion keys, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 90-7562, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, Staging area before taking oath of office, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 90-7563, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, Capitol window view of parade and taking oath, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 90-7564, Inauguration activities for Gov. Wilder, Lt. Gov. Beyers and Attorney General Terry, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 90-7565, 1st Luncheon at the Mansion, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 90-7566, 1st Luncheon at the Mansion, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 90-7567, Governor with children before Inaugural Ball, 1/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 90-7568, Inauguration Weekend Reception at the Mansion, 1/14/1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 90-7569, Gov. Wilder 1st address to Joint Session of General Assembly, 1/15/1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 90-7570, Prayer Service St. Paul's and Opening of the General Assembly, 1/13-15/1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 90-7571, Gov. Wilder Addresses Joint Session of General Assembly, 1/15/1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 90-7612, Proclamation signing for Virginia School Board Association, 1/22/1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 90-7613, Swearing in Secretary of Commonwealth, 1/22/1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 90-7615, St. Mary's presentation to Governor Wilder, 1/22/1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 90-7617, Japanese delegation with Gov. Wilder, 1/23/1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 90-7618, World Access Business group with Gov. Wilder, 1/23/1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- 90-7619, World Access Business group with Gov. Wilder, 1/23/1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 90-7626, Two Russian miners visit Gov. Wilder, 1/24/1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- 90-7627, Executive Order # 4: Education opportunity for all Virginians signed by Gov. Wilder, 1/24/1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- 90-7633, Ambassador Pacvire from Angola visits with Gov. Wilder, 1/25/1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- 90-7634, VSU alumni presented a pen set to Gov. Wilder; A proclamation was signed, 1/25/1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 90-7635, VSU alumni presented a pen set to Gov. Wilder; A proclamation was signed, 1/25/1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- 90-7636, Senator Joanne and family visit Gov. Wilder, 1/25/1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- 90-7652, Presentation of letter of appreciation to Sgt. Jeff Howard by Gov. Wilder, 1/29/1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- 90-7655, Leadership Institute visits Gov. Wilder, 1/30/1990 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- 90-7666, Swearing in Glen Davidson to Virginia Liaison Office, Gov. Wilder attended, 1/30/1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- 90-7672, Gov. Wilder attends Michael Brown swearing in to Board of Elections, 2/1/1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- 90-7678, Gov. Wilder signs a proclamation for the American Heart Association, 2/1/1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- 90-7679, Delegate Whittington W. Clements and Inter-Coop Students visit Gov. Wilder, 2/1/1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- 90-7709, Giles High School History Team with Gov. Wilder, 2/7/1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 90-7727, Senator Emilie F. Miller and Fairfax students visit Gov. Wilder, 2/8/1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 90-7728, Gov. Wilder signs a proclamation for National Engineers Week, 2/8/1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 90-7729, The Black Legislative Caucus and Aides visit Gov. Wilder, 2/8/1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 90-7730, Gov. Wilder signs a proclamation for Vocational Education, 2/8/1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 90-7731, Delegate C. Richard Cranwell and guests visit Gov. Wilder, 2/8/1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 90-7744, Gov. Wilder signs a Letter of Appreciation for AARP, 2/13/1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 90-7745, Gov. Wilder signs a proclamation and receives gifts from exceptional children, 2/13/1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 90-7756, Gov. Wilder signs proclamation for Life Insurance Week, 2/14/1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 90-7757A, Gov. Wilder signs proclamation for Virginia School Principal, 2/14/1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 90-7758, Kiwanis Club High School Seniors visit with Gov. Wilder, 2/14/1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 90-7761, Economic Advisory Commission are being sworn in by Gov. Wilder, 2/15/1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- 90-7774, Courtesy call Partner in America visits Gov. Wilder, 2/16/1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- 90-7775, Courtesy call of Doctor Scott visits with Gov. Wilder, 2/16/1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- 90-7776, Courtesy call of Doctor Scott visits with Gov. Wilder, 2/16/1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- 90-7777, YMCA Youth Governor visits Gov. Wilder, 2/16/1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- 90-7778, Korean businessmen visits Gov. Wilder, 2/16/1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- 90-7785, Gov. Wilder with several members of the staff, 2/20/1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- 90-7786, Easter seal child visit with Gov. Wilder, 2/20/1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- 90-7787, Easter seal child visit with Gov. Wilder, 2/20/1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- 90-7792, Cabinet members: Secretary of Transportation and Education, 2/20/1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- 90-7802, Students from Bridgewater College visit with Gov. Wilder, 2/22/1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- 90-7803, Students of the Model General Assembly visit with Gov. Wilder, 2/22/1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 90-7825, Community Affairs Inova Health System group visits with Gov. Wilder, 2/28/1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- 90-7826, Nauck Civic Association from Arlington visit with Gov. Wilder, 2/28/1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- 90-7828, Gov. Wilder visits display at General Assembly Building, 2/28/1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 90-7830, Gov. Wilder visits Black History Month display at State Library, 2/28/1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- 90-7837, Lt. Gov. Donald Beyer is presented with a check for ABC Incorporated, 2/28/1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- 90-7843, Gov. Wilder opens the DMV Mobile License Vehicle and also receives his new license, 2/28/1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- 90-7844, African America Labor group visit with Gov. Wilder, 3/1/1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- 90-7845, Gov. Wilder signs Virginia Energy Education Day, 3/1/1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- 90-7846, Gov. Wilder visits with people from Del. Ford C. Quillen district, 3/1/1990 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- 90-7847, Gov. Wilder is visited by intern students, 3/1/1990 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- 90-7848, Rolles Royce Inc. officers visit with Governor Wilder, 3/1/1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- 90-7850, Group photo of the 1990 Senate pages in Senate Chamber, 3/2/1990 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- 90-7853, Gov. Wilder signs House Bill 103 sponsored by Del. A. Smith, 3/2/1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- 90-7854, Del. James F. Almand brings students to visit Gov. Wilder, 3/2/1990 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- 90-7867, Congressional members & Legislative members meet with Gov. Wilder, 3/5/1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- 90-7868, Congressional members & Legislative members meet with Gov. Wilder, 3/5/1990 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- 90-7871, Gov. Wilder signs HB 701-E with Del. Jack Kennedy in attendance, 3/5/1990 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- 90-7890, House of Delegates and Senate pages have dinner with Gov. Wilder at the Mansion, 3/7/1990 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- 90-7891, House of Delegates and Senate pages have dinner with Gov. Wilder at the Mansion, 3/7/1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- 90-7892, House of Delegates and Senate pages have dinner with Gov. Wilder at the Mansion, 3/7/1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- 90-7898, Gov. Wilder signs a certificate of recognition for Coast Guard Week, 3/8/1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- 90-7899, Gov. Wilder signs a certificate of recognition for National Wild Life Week, 3/8/1990 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- 90-7913, Shamrock Queen visits with Governor Wilder, 3/9/1990 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- 90-7914, Certificate of Recognition Naval Reserves, 3/9/1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- 90-7915, Picture of portrait of George Mason and Gov. Wilder, 3/9/1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- 90-7918, USAA Manufacture Corporation visit with Gov. Wilder, 3/9/1990 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- 90-7919, House of Delegates staff photo, 3/9/1990 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- 90-7920, Delegate Cranwell and guest visit Gov. Wilder, 3/9/1990 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- 90-7923, Governor Wilder signing bills, 3/10/1990 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- 90-8111, Presentation to Joyce Wilson by Jay Shropshire, 3/16/1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 90-8112, Presentation to Joyce Wilson by Jay Shropshire, 3/16/1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 90-8209, Ambassador from Taiwan, 3/19/1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 90-8218, Management Intern Program, 3/21/1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 90-8219, Ameurop Council Relation Foundation presentation of awards to children by Gov. Wilder, 3/21/1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 90-8220, Ameurop Council Relation Foundation presentation of awards to children by Gov. Wilder, 3/21/1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 90-8223, Certificate for Year Airborne, 3/22/1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 90-8224, Certificate of Recognition of the National Consumer Week, 3/22/1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- 90-8226, Certificate for Year Airborne, 3/22/1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 90-8249, Presentation of group of books to Gov. Wilder, 3/28/1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 90-8313, Week of Young Child Government Conference Room, 4/3/1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 90-8314, National Safe Boating Week, 4/3/1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 90-8315, Richmond Area Marketer Award Certificate, 4/3/1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 90-8322, Proclamation: Manchester Lions Club, 4/4/1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 90-8323, Keep Virginia Beautiful, 4/4/1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 90-8324, American Home Week, 4/4/1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 90-8325, STOP CHILD ABUSE, Dept. of Social Services, 4/4/1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- 90-8346, Gov. Wilder signs a House Bill, 4/10/1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- 90-8347, Students from St. Bridget's school visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/10/1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- 90-8348, Students from St. Bridget's school visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/10/1990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- 90-8349, Governor Wilder signs a House Bill, 4/10/1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 90-8353, Students from Petersburg Elementary visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/11/1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- 90-8354, German Exchange students visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/11/1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- 90-8356, Delegate Shirley F. Cooper and students visit with Gov. Wilder in the House Chambers, 4/11/1990 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- 90-8375, French exchange students from Midlothian High School visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/12/1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- 90-8376, Jay Shropshire meets with Soviet students from JMU, 4/12/1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- 90-8379, Gov. Wilder kicks off the Savings Bond Campaign for state employees, 4/13/1990 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- 90-8380, Gov. Wilder kicks off the Savings Bond Campaign for state employees, 4/13/1990 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- 90-8381, Gov. Wilder kicks off the Savings Bond Campaign for state employees, 4/13/1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- 90-8393, Jimmy L. Reamy and Governor Wilder, Governor's Office Fire Board, 4/13/1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- 90-8448, Gov. Wilder signs HB 86, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- 90-8449, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1100, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- 90-8451, Gov. Wilder signs SB 335, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- 90-8452, Governor's Conference Room Senate Bill 150, Pediatrics, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- 90-8453, Gov. Wilder signs SB 333, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- 90-8454, Gov. Wilder signs 464-465, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- 90-8455, Gov. Wilder signs SB 101, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- 90-8456, Gov. Wilder signs HB 108, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- 90-8457, Gov. Wilder signs HB 626 Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- 90-8458, Gov. Wilder signs SB 479, 481, 483, and 484, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- 90-8459, Gov. Wilder signs SB 467, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- 90-8460, Gov. Wilder signs HB 627, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- 90-8461, Gov. Wilder signs HB 357, 4/18/1990 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- 90-8462, Gov. Wilder signs HB 1096, 4/18/1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 90-8463, Courtesy Call of College Personnel, 4/18/1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 90-8467, Arthur Ashe visits with Gov. Wilder, 4/18/1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 90-8468, Arthur Ashe visits with Gov. Wilder, 4/18/1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 90-8475, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for National Boys and Girls Club, 4/19/1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 90-8476, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Law Day, 4/19/1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 90-8477, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for National Organ Tissue Donor Awareness, 4/19/1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 90-8478, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Extension Homemaker's Week, 4/19/1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 90-8500, Courtesy Call from Dr. Verkuic, President of William and Mary visits with Gov. Wilder, 4/23/1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 90-8501, Courtesy call from Gov. of St. Eustatuis and Honorable and Mrs. Alvin Temmer visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/23/1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 90-8509, Gov. Wilder signs CFR and visits with Holocaust survivors, 4/24/1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 90-8510, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Fetal Awareness Week, 4/24/1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 90-8511, Gov. Wilder visits with students in the Old Senate Chambers, 4/24/1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 90-8512, King's Daughters Hospital and Delegate Jerrauld C. Jones makes a presentation to Gov. Wilder, 4/24/1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- 90-8517, Bill signing HB 1055: Clean Air Act, 4/25/1990 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- 90-8518, Presentation to Gov. Wilder Honorary Membership Theta Psi Chapter, 4/25/1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- 90-8528, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Eastern Shore, 4/26/1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- 90-8529, Courtesy call from Pre-Med students and visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/26/1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- 90-8530, Courtesy call from the Polish Delegation and visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/26/1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- 90-8546, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for the City of Harrisonburg, 4/27/1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- 90-8547, Students from Laurel Ford School visit with Gov. Wilder, 4/27/1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- 90-8557, Courtesy Call Minister Kimura, Embassy of Japan visits with Gov. Wilder, 4/27/1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- 90-8572, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for National Nursing Home Week, 5/1/1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- 90-8573, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Week of the Nurse, 5/1/1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- 90-8574, Gov. Wilder signs CFR Manufactured Housing Month, 5/1/1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- 90-8575, Gov. Wilder signs CFR Certificate of Rec. Hospital Pharmacy Week, 5/1/1990 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- 90-8576, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Volunteer Rescue Squad Week, 5/1/1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- 90-8577, Courtesy call at the Gov.'s Office, 5/1/1990 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- 90-8578, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Secretary's Week, 5/1/1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- 90-8579, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Kiddies Week, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- 90-8580, Gov. Wilder signs SB 83, 188, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- 90-8583, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Egg Council, 4/30/1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- 90-8612, Gov. Wilder signs HB 129, 560, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- 90-8613, Gov. Wilder signs HB188, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- 90-8614, Gov. Wilder signs HB 310, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- 90-8615, Gov. Wilder signs SB 179, 332, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- 90-8618, Gov. Wilder signs HB 56, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- 90-8619, Gov. Wilder signs HB 176, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- 90-8620, Gov. Wilder signs HB 461, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- 90-8621, Gov. Wilder signs HB 674, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- 90-8622, Gov. Wilder signs HB 808, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- 90-8623, Gov. Wilder signs 839, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- 90-8624, Gov. Wilder signs SB 204, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- 90-8625, Gov. Wilder signs SB 235, 5/3/1990 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- 90-8644, Gov. Wilder signs HB 678, 5/7/1990 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- 90-8645, Students from R.C. Logan School visit with Gov. Wilder at Capitol, 5/8/1990 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- 90-8646, Gov. Wilder presents a plaque to the Nurse of the Year, 5/8/1990 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- 90-8647, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for Foster Care Week, 5/8/1990 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- 90-8648, MS Awards are presented by Gov. Wilder, 5/8/1990 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- 90-8649, Gov. Wilder presents a scholarship to Presoila B. Lapada Jr., 5/8/1990 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- 90-8650, Gov. Wilder presents a scholarship to Presoila B. Lapada Jr., 5/8/1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 90-8688, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Working Women Awareness Week, 5/11/1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 90-8689, Gov. Wilder presents awards to Correction Officers, 5/11/1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 90-8690, Gov. Wilder presents awards to Correction Officers, 5/11/1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- 90-8692, Little Miss Poppie makes a visit to Gov. Wilder, 5/9/1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- 90-8709, Gov. Wilder signs SB 253, 5/15/1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 90-8718, John Phellips presents two photographs to Gov. Wilder, 5/16/1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 90-8719, Louise Briehl presents a painting to Gov. Wilder, 5/16/1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 90-8720, Exchange Rotarians and Richmond Rotarians visit with Gov. Wilder, 5/16/1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- 90-8725, A group from Roanoke made a courtesy call on Gov. Wilder, 5/17/1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 90-8726, Gov. Wilder signs CFR for National Insurance Week, 5/17/1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 90-8727, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Older Virginians, 5/17/1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- 90-8774, Gov. Wilder signs a CFR for Virginia Rivers Month, 5/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)